I'm mad drunk right and one member of
the cast suggests that I go take a
on the cup
[Music]
[Applause]
welcome sit this is not happening to
present world of blunder interpret this
show before this is a bunch of comics
telling fun stories about real that
happened give it out very very funny
then mr. David Koechner everybody
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah this is eight years ago my travel
story I traveled to Louisiana to make
money for my family I have five kids now
we have five kids now at the time we had
to go down there I knew some of the cast
member so it was a fun thing not too
long all right get down there day before
the principal shooting photography I'm
not gonna tell you what film of this I'm
gonna change names as we go through
because I'd like to keep working so get
down there and my friend MC he and I are
would stay in the same hotel and write
out the hotel about I don't know four
blocks across a parking lot a couple of
restaurants so we have a couple three
four beers gonna call it a night all
right it's like 8:30 Louisiana time
heading back and we run into some more
of the cast heading into another
establishment near the first
establishment they say come with us like
ah okay we go in there now these kids
are younger than I am and they're having
car bombs right so that's that's a nail
of some kind and then you drop a shot in
it I have three or four of those they go
down easy
I've been doing it a long time
I'm better at this than anybody you know
[Applause]
it's not a joke that's a tail my liver
tells so at this point it's 9 o'clock
Louisiana time which means it's 7
o'clock
la time so I'm gonna go outside call
home and tuck my kids in I'm a good dad
thank you oh so I'm not there I'm
speaking to my wife talking to the kids
like I said we had to at the time fine
fine now I have just had I don't know
how many beers and I'd not go into the
bathroom so I kind of there's a parking
lot here I go this other like abandoned
parking lot area where there's a few
bushes and I start relieving myself so
I'm getting near the end of my relief
and I see a car pulls up I'm like really
here there's plenty of spots closer to
the restaurant why is this dick parking
here we want to watch this okay so I
shake it off and zip it up still on the
phone with my wife
and out star out steps to police
officers oh hello guys let's commemorate
all right he writes me a ticket for
public urination as he should
I'm fine with that great drunk all right
hey but then he tells me I have a court
date oh my god just pay it no you got up
here yeah I don't I don't live here I
don't care you had to peer
yeah yeah look I'm sorry but I don't
live here not gonna fly back in two
months to do this and okay I got a pad
now I'm mad drunk right no so I go
inside
and there's this table of about 20
people from the cast and crew having
more drinks or whatever and I'm pretty
upset and I'm telling my friends about
it and one member of the cast suggests
that I go take a on the cop car to
him that seemed appropriate revenge
let's balance this thing out here you
gotta come back well clearly he deserves
a turd on his car I kind of think about
it
I head outside and my buddy MC follows
me out cuz he'd seen what was going on
in my eye and he goes Koechner you get
your I comply yes sir
you're right I'm gonna go to the hotel
short walk short stumble over so I'm
there and a couple hours later I'm in my
hotel room and the door opens someone's
letting himself into my hotel room I'm
like what the hell people are coming in
my room I'm like what the hell's going
on and I'm hungover at this point right
it's two o'clock in the morning and I
see four police officers enter the room
and I'm like what what's going on I
think it's man you guys take this
piece in public really serious there you
go or we're gonna go downtown
I'm like why you wrote me a ticket
what's going on you know like I don't
know so they they handcuff me and then
they throw a t-shirt over me and then I
get in the police car with the gentleman
that wrote me the ticket and I'm like
what is going on guys he's like uh-huh
and so I see these cop cars the other
three take off this way when we take off
another way and then we're kind of like
on a county road not the regular road
I'm like dude what's going on what's
going on I'm sorry I shouldn't have
pissed in the parking lot I you but you
gave me the ticket I don't know what's
going on oh is that all you did like I
yeah what do you what's going on you
know but I'm like honestly was just
flabbergasted God's name has happened
and been pinned on me so I get there to
the station thank God and they put me in
a chair yeah it's not safe for the back
of a cop car so they put me in the
interrogation room and some guy comes in
is like go well you guys save yourself
like I don't know I got a ticket I don't
I what is this a joke is this a prank is
this some kind of prank thing because I
have to work in the morning early and
this is not I'm not this is not funny
uh-huh all right well we heard something
about someone on after you left the bar
that right like I don't know I left the
bar I went home oh did you we've heard
otherwise what the so then that
happens they sent another guy in then
they sent a young guy in I know you
I like your movies it tries to warm up
to me right he's super good cop I'm
gonna confess whatever to and they've
got me handcuffed to a pipe
right and I'm like what is going on here
ghost you really don't know huh you
really don't know I said I don't know
please someone explain why the you
drug me out of my hotel room and put me
to the station two o'clock in
the morning and then they opened the
door to the interrogation room and then
they opened the door to an office on the
other side where the police officers are
gathered around the phone
put it on speaker they got the waitress
from the establishment on the phone all
right go ahead and tell us what you saw
well I see their faces drop a little bit
like Oh our case is kind of unraveling
well tell us now you saw some no no they
just all talking about it there at the
table so here's what had happened in my
absence the one gentleman who had
insisted that I should probably on
the cop car then was kind of wildly
exclaiming that I had done it and then
apparently several people at the at the
table went and started looking at the
cop car like this you know where did it
happen where did it happen which in this
waitress was a friend of the police
officers and she went right to their
table and said the guy he gave a ticket
to on your car Chicka Chicka cuff
cuff what's going on so anyway she
didn't see anything like guys I didn't
anywhere I didn't in your cop
car nothing happened all right so they
let me go now the lieutenant of the
bunch whoever the guy is I think he's a
lieutenant drives me home he asked me a
couple of times did you do it
what if you're asking if I urinated in
public yes did I anywhere no okay
so he walks me up to my room right he
doesn't just go okay get out we go up to
my room and then he's leaning in the
door jamb here I'm like man I gotta
sleep I gotta work in two hours now then
you know my trade I look good that's my
thing
Fatty's got to look good on camera and
he's just chatting with me like
would you submit to a DNA test
what will someone show me the on
this car I go yeah those okay he's like
yeah who'd you vote for
right man
so I'm an actor so I do a little bit of
this you know it doesn't matter who we
voted for cuz we're all Americans let me
tell you another thing I would never do
what you thought happened out there I
have a brother-in-law that's in the
force you guys do day in and day out I'm
sorry that this havoc is upon you go on
I'm like what the
okay next morning I had to get
up at 6:00 there blah blah it was like
oh so I tell one of these people like
what the did you guys do after I
left because I got hauled out of
my hotel room taken downtown bla bla bla
like wow so now this is the first day of
shooting right so who are the am i
I'm the that shits in cars
I know a lot of these people well most
of my doubt so I'm seeing this kind of
stuff and so as filming goes on the
principal actress in the movie never
quite warmed up to me we had a couple of
scenes together and I'm a nice guy and I
don't mind talking to people but this
girl would only give yes or no answers
to my constant interrogation in an
attempt to start a conversation that's
like oh well I don't give a
I'll talk to anybody else I'll talk to
myself if I have to how you doing
anyway I have to hire a local lawyer go
down there he was able to move the trial
up so I up here I think whole thing cost
me $500 between him and the rest of the
business I go home six months later I
get a call from an actor buddy of mine
who was now working with his principal
actress and another movie and he says
actor what now did you do in
Louisiana I didn't do anything
what you hear well the way I heard it is
you got a DWI cops hauling you down the
station and you're in the back and you
your pants
[Applause]
[Music]
david koechner everybody david koechner
thank you very much for doing it man
don't forget to check him out in
anchorman 2 so last week I asked you
guys to post stories of your father
something in the comment section about
some crazy your father did and here's
one of the really good ones that we saw
next week in honor of David Koechner
story tell me something about the law
some trouble you've gotten into with the
cops I know you have some good stories
on this I know that I have to generate
fans so close your best story is right
down there in the comments section thank
you guys for tuning in don't forget to
hashtag this is not happening on Twitter
follow me on twitter at Ari Shaffir and
leave comments and tell your friends
about all these all these videos and
spread the word we'll make it even more
of them
[Music]